很久很久以前-九月份
A long,long time ago--September
在一个很远的地方-长岛
in a place far,far away--Long Island
三个孩子面临他们对生活的挑战
three children faced the challenge of their young lives
-开学第一天！
--the first day of school."
一百万学生第一天返回学校
One million students report back for first day of school.
二百万家长开怀大笑。
Two million parents giggle hysterically with glee.
我看不到中午你就会感到寂寞了！
I bet it's so quiet around here,you'll miss them by noon.
哈哈哈……
(hysterical laughter)hahaha.
又受气了？
New pants?
我病了！
I'm sick.
刚才你吃三块碎饼的时候不是蛮好的吗？
Well,you didn't seen so sick when you ate those three waffles.
没准我就是吃碎饼吃坏了。
Maybe I got wholesome bad syrup.
知道我怎么想？
You know what I think?
好，我去上学。
Yeah,I'm going to school.
开学第一天可是个大喜日子。
Alright! This is going to be a great day or what?
你对开学好像特别的兴奋。
You're excited about the first day of school?
对。
Yes.
BEN，你看Mike，连他也急着要去学校上课了。
Ben! Look at Mike. Even he's anxious to get to school.
对，我现在已经进高班了，这说明什么？
Yeah,it's the beginning of my junior year. Don't you know what that means?
说明我更成熟了
It means I am more mature now,
说明更有责任心了
means I am more responsible,
说明只有两年我就能摆脱这鬼地方了。
means that in less than two years I'm going to be getting out of that dump!
我看只有书呆子对开学才会感到特别的兴趣。
Only a yo yo would be excited about the first day of school.
大家早上好啊。
Good morning all!
Carol，这套新衣服挺漂亮。
Carol,your new outfit looks great.
会不会--太性感？
It's not too...sexy?
也许在保加利亚时。
Ah,maybe for Bulgaria.
你看上去确实很美。
I think you look terrific.
我是想有个好的开端
Yeah,well,I just want to get on the right foot.
我是说，新的学年，新的挑战，新的衣服，新的朋友……
I mean,a new year,new challenges,new clothes,new friends..
新的脓疱。
New zits.
Mike，Carol，车来了。
Mike! Carol! The bus.
再见
Bye sweetie,bye.
再见妈妈。
See you late mum.
等一下Mike。
Hold it Mike.
什么？
What?
你都准备好了？
You're all ready for school?
是。
Yes.
你妹妹拿好了书本
Well your sister has her books,
笔记本纸张铅笔讲义夹绘图仪器。
notebooks,paper,pencils,binders,course dividers…
行了，妈妈我知道你的用意
Mum,mum,I know where you are going here.
准备好的又不是只有Carol一个人。
Now Carol's not the only one who's prepared for school.
我的表现是内在的。
I'm just not a fanatic.
你说说上课前你都准备了些什么。
Now what have you done to prepare for school?
好吧，可以，今晚有个开学舞会对吧？
Alright,alright! Tonight,there is a welcome back dance.
我已经找好了舞伴。
I have already got myself a date.
-= Subripped by Susie Shi =-       2007.07.16
（广播）全体来报到的同学请安静，大家注意了，
Attention Dewey Highers.
上课取消了--这是开玩笑。
Hello,school is cancelled. Just kidding!
现在，大家注意了
But now I have your attention,
填好表格签到，
have all your forms filled out and signed.
在收到课表后到。。。
After you receive your schedule go to...
Mike? Mickey?
Mike?
Eddie,你好吗？好久没见了。
Eddie,my man. How you doing? Long time no see.
你挺神气的哥们。
You're looking good.
咳咳，先生们。
Hu hmmmm! Gentleman.
Boner,见到你很高兴。
Boner! Good to see you man. Hey hey.
你鼻子下是什么？
What's that on your face?
这是我的胡子。
This? A moustache.
你上星期还没长呢？
A moustache! It wasn't there last week.
我是意大利人。
I'm Italian.
原来是画上去的。
No,no,it's drawn on!
不是画上去，是快速长。本来就长了不少。
It's not drawn on. It's Axel. It's a jungle of hair.
你父母见了怎么说？
What do your parents think about this
他们还没发现。
They haven't noticed yet.
Hi Mike.
Mike。
艾拉。
Oh,hi Elaine.
舞会见还是你来接我？
Are we meeting at the dance or are you picking me up?
这个排头我还有
Come on Elaine! I'm a class dude.
当然是我来接，
Of course I'm going to pick you up.
回头见。
See you!
再见。
Bye bye.
Mike，Mike，你要带她去跳舞吗？
Mikey,Michael. You are taking Elaine Dooley to the dance?
我没对你们提起过？
Oh didn't I mention that to you guys?
是她打赌输给你了？
What,did she like lose a bet or something?
不不，老实说，我对她做了一个暑假的工作。
No. You know I have been working on that girl all summer long.
我和她已经打下了深刻的实质性的基础。
Laying down the basis for a deep and meaningful relationship,
这是建立在理解、信任和相互……哗，
that's based on trust,understanding,and mutual..wow!
那漂亮妞是谁？
Who's that fox over there?
我去。我优先。
I've got her.  I've got dibs on her.
是我先发现的。
I said it first.
Mike，你已经有艾拉了。
You got Elaine.
抱歉，兄弟们，我得去会会这位姑娘。
If you'll excuse me boys,I have to meet this creature.
Mike，你不是说你和艾拉的关系很深了吗？
Hey Mike,I thought you had some deep,personal relationship going here.
这种事你长大了就会知道，
That's something else you learn as you grow older Eddie.
请记住有意种花花不开这话。
Relationships don't always turn out as you planned.
功课很重？
Tough schedule kid.
对，新学期功课是很重的。
Well yeah,it's a brand new year,
我要接受这一挑战。
and it wanted it to be a challenge.
你可以出去了！
Get out of here.
你有什么
What did you ..
课程？对！是
Get?  Right!  Uh hu!
我有物理和拉丁对话。
Algebra two,physics,conversational Latin..
我们一样。
Wow! We got the same...
课程表！
Schedule. Uh hu!
五年了，都这样。
Right! Fifth year!
对!恩!好极了。恩
Right!Uh hu!  Great!Uh hu!
现在只有九点。
Good! Well,it's only nine thirty.
今天的任务还多着呢。
Things could still happen.
就在这，216室，
This is it. Room two sixteen.
比上学期的教室好多了，对吗BEN？
This is a nicer classroom than you had last year. Isn't it Ben?
Ben?
BNE？
有什么问题吗？
Honey is something wrong?
没有。
No. No!
没有？别瞎跑，
Well don't play around.
我要见见你们老师，我上班要迟到了。
I want to meet your teacher and I'm already late for work.
马克。
Mark!
BEN。你终于还是来了。
Ben! You actually showed up.
他在这吗？
Is he here?
我没有看见他。
I haven't seen him.
你好，我是Maggie Seaver，Ben的母亲。
Hello,I'm Maggie Seaver. Ben's mother.
Maggie Seaver？，Mike的母亲？
Maggie Seaver! You're Mike's mother!
是的。噢，是卡特老师！我怎么没有认出你来。
Yes! Oh,Mrs Conner,I didn't recognize you.
呵呵。你倒还记得我？
But you remembered me.
因为我记得Mike。
I remembered Mike!
路易还在这个班上吗？
Is Louis Vasco in this class?
路易？
Louis Vasco?
大个的。
Big kid.
不在。
No.
好极了！
Alright!
我也不知道究竟怎么了，
Excuse me Mrs Conner. I don't know what's going on,
BEN对开学上课好像不大愿意。
but Ben has been a littlehesitant about coming back to school,and he..
这一点他很像Mike。
He is a lot like Mike.
是吗?你还真幸运。
Boy,are you lucky!
你错了。你还真遗憾他不在这个学校。
Are you kidding? I'm sorry he's not at this school.
本少爷准备好了。
This kid was ready.
BEN，你怎么了。
Honey,how are you feeling?
好吧。
Fine!
我没有不舒服？
Are you alright?
没有。
Great!
那很好。再见，宝贝。
Well good! Bye honey,have a good day.
BEN，我刚听说了，
Ben! I just found out.
路易还在这个学校里。
Louis Vasco is at this school.
什么？
What?
是的，他留级了。
Yeah,he flunked.
而且他还是很坏！
And he's still mean.
他会杀了你的BEN。
He's going to kill you,Ben.
这暑假，你好好过。
Enjoy your summer,Seaver face.
你以后再没机会了。
It's going to be your last one.
等再开学了，你死定了，
When we get back to school,you're dead meat.
听见了？！你死定了！
Hear me? Dead meat.
死定了！死定了！
Dead meat. Dead meat.
什么事这么急？！
Hey,what's the rush cowboy?
艾迪，我没有时间了。
Hey,look Eddie,I have no time. Alright?
今天上午上物理课要解剖青蛙。
Oh,of course. You don't want to be late for Biology on frog day.
算了。我找金发女郎。
Eddie,the blonde.
又见了？
Again?
打了个照面。
Eye contact.
快追。
Go!
好
Yes!
上午11点
Well it's still eleven am.
今天还没到十一点倒霉的事就这么多。
There's still a chance for thing to get better.
她不见了。
She's gone.
噢，Carol，你的书掉了。
Oh Carol,did you drop your books?
让我来帮你捡吧，Carol。
Hey,I'm sorry. Here let me help,Carol.
帮个忙
Oh,speaking of help.
和你上历史课的那个金头发的叫什么来的？
I need to know the name of the blonde in your history class.
有一个叫罗杰·甫洛美。
Well,there's Roger Frommin.
不，Carol，我是说姑娘们。
No,Carol,I mean the girls.
哦，是佩吉·斯帕基
Oh,Becky Swarking.
长扒牙的佩吉，
Buck tooth Becky?
隔着门洞能啃玉米棒子的姑娘？
The one who could eat corn on the cob through a knot hole?
不，Carol，我是说一个很迷人的姑娘，
No Carol,this girl was a living dream.
新来的。
She's new.
没有发现什么新来的姑娘，
Well,I didn't see any new girl.
都是原来那些老同学老面孔。
Just the same kids,face after face.
全都是老面孔，老同学，老面孔。
After face,after face,after face...
好了，玩笑开完了哥们，你太有趣了。
Ok,jokes over! Very funny,ha ha.
波拿？
Boner?
Hello Mike.
Mike！
波拿你在里面干什么？
Hey,come on. What are you doing in there?
奇克关我的，
Cheech locked me in.
他妒忌我的这把胡子。
I think he was jealous of my moustache.
真是怪人。
What a jerk!
帮我复习历史吧。
Got me out of history.
你帮帮忙吧，我还要考生物呢。
Oh,come on Mike. We got Biology.
一排不能少两个
Can't miss two in a row.
噢，她在那！谁？
There she is.Who?
再见波拿。
I'll see you later Bone.
Mike，我不想生物也开红灯，
Mike! I don't want to go to Biology alone.
奇克要笑我的。
Cheech is there! Oh!
嗨!
Hi!Hi!
Bonjour people. I'm coach Lovick;
同学们好，我是辅导老师罗克。
I'll be covering French three while Mademoiselle Goldstein
我来代替他上法语课。
is a little bit under the weather.
格罗斯塔老师身体不好
Grab a desk mone sure.
回到座位上去，同学。
Tres bon sport.
要我罚你蹲一课吗？
Ok I believe today is a little review of French two,
这很好，同学们。好吧，同学们，今天我们就来复习法语课。
so what I'm going to do...Speak!
所以我们……你说吧。
Mademoiselle Goldstein fait toujours son cours toute on francais.
（法语）
Ah ha! Uhhh,can anybody here translate that for us?
谁能把刚才这位讲的法语翻译一下吗？你！
You.
她说格罗斯塔老师全部用法语上课的。
She said Mrs Goldstein always conducts our class in French.
棒，很好。
Ah bon,very tres bon.
现在我们就请这位姑娘来跟我们大家说说
Um,say what we'll do is we'll have this young lady stand up here
她在暑假里的所见所闻吧。
and tell us what she did for her summer vacationay.
现在请继续说吧。
Come and tely vous them.
好吧。（法语）
Ok,Eh bien,for mes vacances d'ete,je suis aller a Disney Land,ce qui m'a
beaucoup c'amuse. 'ai voulons selon Mickie et aussi Goofie. Apres,je suis aller au
chaud de Jonney Journee etait tres amusant.oh,j'ai rencontrait un garcon qui s'appelle...
对不起，我想和你说几句话。
I'm sorry,but I just had to meet you.
现在不行，Mike。
Shhhhh! Not now Mike.
你认识我？！
You've heard of me?
等一会！
Shhh! Later.
什么时候？
When?
明晚八点在舞会上。
Meet me at the dance tonight at eight.
那好吧，咱们说定了。
Ah Ok. It's a date. It's a date.
我很高兴。可我还不知道你的名字呢。
Wait a minute. I don't even know your name.
同学，
Hey buddy!
你的法语太好了，不用上了是不是？
You talk French so good you don't need this?
法语，这不是生物课吗？
French! You mean this isn't biology?
出去，出去，出去！再见吧先生，再见。
Out! Out! Bonjour monsieur. Adios!
讲完了？
Are you done?
是的
Oui Oui.
现在你自己再翻译一下。
No you should have thought about that before class.
好极了，Mike，今晚的舞会你一定会出尽风头的。
Alright Seaver. You have got yourself one hot date for the dance.
Mike。晚上见。
Hi Mike. See you tonight.
那当然。
You bet.
我遇到麻烦了。
I got a problem.
什么麻烦。
What kind of problem?
一举腿
Lift those legs,girls.
举过了。
I'm lifting.
二伸腿
Tighten those thighs
我在伸
I'm tightening.
紧缩臀部。
Firm that bottom.
我没放松过。
I'm still tightening.
非常好。现在做扩胸动作。
Very good. Now the chest.
把你少女时代的发育不足都弥补起来好吗？
Let's make up for all those years of going braless shall we?
一，二，一，二，一，二
And one and two and one and two and one..
(phone rings)
你歇会吧。
Hold that thought.
喂？我是BEN的父亲。
Hello. Yeah this is Ben's father.
这种事他不会干的。
Well that doesn't sound like Ben.
好，我马上来。
Alright,I'll be right over.
扩胸还没见效呢。
Where did I leave my bra?
Carol，我们给你留着位子。
Carol,we saved your old seat.
好。
Uh hu.
我说，现在，又是一个新的学年，
Well,see,this is a new year
咱们在一块吃午饭也很久了。
and I thought that we'd been at lunch together for so long
结识新朋友对大家都有好处。
that new people would be good for us.
天啊。
Wow,you're like.
这话像是赶我们！
Dumping us?
对。
Right.
呃。
Uh hu.
我是说这不一样。
Cause,I mean it wouldn't be the same.
我们从5年级就在一起吃饭了。
We've eaten lunch together since the fifth grade.
4年级。
Forth.
对
Right.
像这么大的变化我确实很难适应。
Uh hu. And I don't deal well with major change.
我坐这里。
I'll sit,I'll sit.
算了，算了。
Alright.
恩。
Uh hu.
天啊，两个女孩肯让你分享，真是带劲！
Wow,that must be great to find two women who'll share you like that.
波拿，她们还不知道。别说傻话。
Boner they don't know. Don't be so stupid.
说我傻？
I'm stupid!
你和两个女孩约会还说我傻瓜。
You've got a date with two girls,and I'm stupid?
我是有点傻瓜。
I am stupid.
你打算甩掉哪个？
So who are you going to cut loose Mikey?
听着，艾迪，我要去和艾拉聊聊，
Eddie,I'm going to go over there and I'm going to talk to Elaine
我要非常婉转地向她说明。
and I'm going to let her down very gently and very easily.
把她扔过垃圾堆里是吗？
End of the dumperoo,right?
看我的。
Watch me?
他来了
He comes.
艾拉。
Ah,Elaine.
Oh Mike,hi!
Mike。
能和你聊聊吗？
Could we talk for a minute?
想坐下吗？
Did you want to sit?
不不，我就呆一会。我说。
No,no,I can't stay. So.
什么？
What?
你知道我应该向你说明。
You know I should just tell you.
是关于舞会的事？
Is it about the dance?
对。
Yeah.
我真兴奋。
I am so excited.
等会我穿新衣服给你看。
Wait until you see the new outfit I got.
你买新衣服了？
You got a new outfit?
对，款式还挺新颖，
Yeah,and it's really hot.
是特意在时装世界买的。
I got it at Chadwick's department store.
那是一家有名的商店，退货是比较方便的。艾拉。
Great store. You know very liberal return policy. Elaine.
我脑子里只有舞会，整天都在想。
All I've been able to think about all day is the dance.
我们想的也太巧了。
What a coincidence.
你遇上的姑娘我找到了。在204教室。
Mike,I found her,the dream girl. Room two o four.
204，好极了。
Two o four. Great. Thanks Eddie.
如果我是你，我不会甩掉金发女孩，我会甩掉艾拉。
Now,if I were you,I wouldn't dust the blonde. I'd dump Elaine.
我不是甩掉谁，
No,no no. I'm not dusting the blonde.
只是迟缓一个星期。
I'm just putting her on hold till next week.
等一下。算了现在我就告诉你，听着。
Alright. Hey Eddie,tell me how does it sound like?
HI，我这样做也许太冒失了一点，
Hi. Call me crazy but this just can't wait.
这件事，我知道没有任何一件事没和它相比，
I think we've got something really special here between us,
而且我又不愿意和那些平庸的同学做伴，
and I don't want to share it with a bunch of high school kids at a dance.
下星期咱们俩一块出去怎么样？
So what do you say that you and me go out instead next week,
就咱们俩。
just the two of us.
Hi!
HI，
Hi.
我说我这样做也许太冒失了点，这件，
Look,call me crazy,nut this just couldn't wait.
我知道没有任何一件……
You know I think we've got something…
Hi Mike.
HI，Mike
你是个非常不一般的……
Hi Elaine. Something really special..
等会再说。呵呵。
.It could wait,after all.
你可以和他谈到课间休息结束。
You can talk to him in here till recess ends.
谢谢。
Thanks.
天啊，人小，
Boy,when you're small,
别人连叫你父母都不征求一下你的意见。
people don't even ask you if you want your parents called.
我知道你想转学到另一个学校去。
So I understand you want to be transferred to another school.
对，不错，这地方越来越旧了。
Yeah,well this place is getting kind an old.
恐怕这很困难。
Well that would be difficult.
因为让你转学的唯一办法是我们必须
You see for you to go to another school,
搬家。
we've got to move to another district.
这困难很大吗？
Is that a problem?
当然。
Yes.
有办法了。转到犹太学校。
I got it! How about Hebrew school?
你还是告诉你那男孩干嘛要和你过不去？
How about you telling me why some kid wants to fight with you?
你听说了？
You heard?
是的。
Uh hu.
那男孩的名字叫路易·瓦斯可，
See,there is this big mean kid,Louis Vasco.
上学期我不肯给他作弊。
And last year I wouldn't let him cheat off me.
那你做得对啊。
Well good for you.
可他给我捎信来了。三点钟男厕所。
He sent a message. "Three o clock. Boys bathroom".
BEN，这就有点不正常了。
Ben this is so strange.
你是说该在女厕所较量？
Well he wouldn't meet me in the girl's bathroom.
不，我是说你这件事
No I mean this whole situation.
我以前也碰到过你信不信？
Would you believe the same thing happened to me?
算了吧爸爸。
Come on dad.
我的话你不信？
You don't believe me?
就会对我讲老一套的事。
You are going to do like you always do
又是说你当时没有临阵逃脱，
and tell me some story about how you didn't run
最后你们却成了好朋友。
and you ended up being friends.
不，我逃掉了。
No,I ran.
什么？
What?
那时我十一岁，
I was eleven years old
想加入一个叫加油工的垒球队
and I was trying out for this baseball team-The Oilers.
当时要在我和另外一个男孩中间选一个打第三垒的。
Well it came right down to me or this other boy for the third base position.
叫他男孩并不准确，
Well boy wasn't really right.
那人是个高头大马，
This boy was a gorilla.
人家叫他杀手。
They called him Killer.
你怎么对他的。
What did you do?
我放弃了。我没打球整整一年。
I quit. I didn't play baseball that whole year.
从那以后，我和他一别就是
Anyway I didn't see killer again for
十五年，后来我们又见面了。
fifteen years. And I saw him at a reunion.
他有了啤酒肚，不能运动。
He had a big beer belly. All athletes end up with beer bellies.
那天我和你妈妈在一起，杀手的真名字是拉夫……
I was there with you mum,and killer,whose real name was Ralph.
爸爸，你想说什么？
Dad,what's your point?
你听着，他告诉我他很高兴当年我没和他对着干。
Well the point is he told me he was glad I didn't fight him that day.
为什么？
Why?
因为他怕我就像我怕他的程度一样。
Well because he was just as afraid of me as I was of him.
大个子他也怕？
Big guys are afraid too?
当然了。
Yes.
就是说我该向男子汉那样面对现实？
So you are saying that I should face this guy like a man?
说得对！
That's right.
万一你真的招架不住的话，
And if that doesn't work and he starts to hit you,
再溜也不迟。
then you run like the wind.
请问
Oh excuse me!
今晚舞会你有伴吗？
Do you by any chance have a date for tonight's dance?
你有空吗？
Pardon me,but I uh..Hi.
你干嘛不肯跟我去跳舞？！
Why won't anyone go to the dance with me?
对不起Carol，我以为是其他姑娘。
Sorry Carol. I thought you was just a regular girl.
下午两点事情有好转。
Two pm and things are not getting better.
我放弃，我难过极了，
I give up. I'm sorry,
我想来点新的办法可又不灵。
I thought I'd try something new but it didn't work.
告诉我怎么回事。
Tell me about it.
我一切都没进展。
Nothing ever changes for me.
波拿。我了解你现在的心情。
Boner. I know exactly how you feel.
像丧家狗。
Like dog drool.
我希望你今天能够有所不同。
I was expecting today to be different too.
反正我是个不受欢迎的人。
I was stupid enough to think that I could get a date.
噢，我倒是可以帮你来点新的
All I wanted was something new.
来点不同的来点不一般的……
Something different,something unusual.
如果我同意和你去跳舞的话
If I um,did agree to go to this dance with you,
可我现在没有同意，但你得答应一些条件。
which I haven't,you'd have to agree to certain conditions.
什么都行。
Anything.
不准握手。不准跳得太慢但又不准跳得太快。
No hand holding. No slow dancing,no fast dancing..
如果你同意和我去，我甚至可以不上场。
And if you agree to go with me,I don't even have to show up.
真的吗？
Do I ?
当然。
No.
那好吧那就这么说定了。
Well Ok,you've got your date.
你身上确实有不一般的东西。
And you've got something uh unusual.
路易？！
Louis?
Seaver小子！
Seaver Face.
我听说你在找我。
I hear you've been looking for me.
对。
Yeah?
现在我来了！
So I'm here.
怎么了？你害怕进来了？
What's the matter? Afraid to come in?
是你害怕出来！
You're afraid to come out. Woos.
爸爸说得真对！
Dad was right.
好，你这个小…你长高了。
Alright you little....you grew.
你没有。
You didn't.
我想是我的车了。
I think that's my bus.
看吧BEN，路易这小子害怕你了。
Wow Ben. He was actually afraid of you.
说得对，马克，每个人都害怕别人，
Yeah well Mark. Everybody's a little bit frightened.
就看你有没有勇气。
Even big guys like me.
我不想伤任何人的心，
Now I don't want to break Elaine's heart.
And I sure don't want to upset the blonde.
所以我就应该定一个比较婉转的办法把其中一个姑娘打发走。
So uh,it's out of my hands and the next girl who walks round the corner,
波拿，波拿。
is history. Ah Boner,boner..
我知道你有麻烦。
I know. Get lost.
Mike你怎么了？
Mike. What happened?
体操场，下蹲时扭伤了。
Ah,gym class. I misfired on a power squat.
是吗？
No!
对，今晚我得让医生看看。
Yeah! Look,I have to see a doctor,tonight.
你不能去跳舞了？
So the dance is out?
是的。我非常抱歉。
Yeah,I am really sorry Elaine,
但我身体一好一定陪你去玩。
but I promise we will go out just as soon as I'm home.
我希望你能谅解。
I hope you understand?
我能谅解。我能帮你什么忙吗？
Of Course I do. Is there anything I can do to help?
不，不必了，还是让我自己走好了。
No,I'd rather you not see me like this,ok.
好吧，你当心点。
Ok,take care!
知道了，再见。
You too. Bye bye.
Hi.
HI，
是你？！
You!
是我。
Me.
听着，我非常荣幸，今晚咱们是第一次约会，
Look,I'm a class dude,and I don't want to meet my date at the dance,
我开车来接你怎么样？
so what do you say I pick you up?
约会？我们的约会？
Date? We don't have a date.
你答应去跳舞的。
Yes we do,for the dance tonight.
不，我是说舞会上见。
No,I just said I'd see you there.
噢，等一下。
Ah wait a minute.
我明白了，你有比我强的人就把我扔了！啊！
I get it! You've found someone you like better and you're dumping me.
不，我绝不会干那种卑鄙的事，你呢？
Oh no! I could never do something like that. Could you?
不不不，这个问题咱们还是别说了。
Ah,don't you change the subject here.
Mike，你完全误解了。
Mike,you misunderstood.
我没有误解。你知道我为你做了多大的牺牲。
Misunderstood! Are you...do you have any idea what I gave up for you?
我并没有要求你这样去做呀。
I didn't ask you to give anything up.
老实说吧，我回绝了一个姑娘，是为了和你去跳舞。
I'll tell you what,I gave up Elaine Dooley,for a date with you.
Mike！我不和你约会，是因为我并不信任你。
Mike. I couldn't date you. I don't even trust you.
你在说不信任我之前最好先了解我。
Look! Before you mistrust me,I suggest you get to know me.
我很了解你，Mike。
I do know you Mike.
怎么可能？
From where?
记得去年的野餐会吗？
Do you remember the class picnic last year?
不不不，你没参加我当然不记得。
No,no. You weren't there. I would have remembered you.
我来提示一下，
I can prove I was there.
你模仿贝琪拔牙的腔调，弄得哄堂大笑还记得吗？
You did that really funny impression of buck tooth Becky Swarking. Remember?
请把玉米递给我。
Pass the corn please.
哈哈，挺滑稽的！
Very funny!
……贝琪？！过了一个暑假你完全变了！
Becky? Boy you have had quite a summer.
今天该你出洋相了！
And you have had quite a fall.
HI，亲爱的。
Hi guys.
Hi.
HI。
我说JASON，今天你感到寂寞吗？
So Jason,were you lonely today?
HI，BEN，今天开学第一天学到点什么？
And Ben. What did you learn your first day back?
我学到了进犹太学校也不解决问题。
I learned that Hebrew school is not the answer.
一会儿跟你解释。
I'll explain later.
我说Carol，你今天一切都很顺利吗？
So Carol. Was today everything you hoped it would be?
开关有点不太妙可后来就很顺利。
Well it started out a little shaky,but it ended up ok.
好，很好。
Good.
甚至有人约我去跳舞。
I even have a date for the dance.
好极了。
Great!
最棒的是，我甚至可以不上场。
And the best part is,I don't even have to go.
你回来晚了，去哪了？
Mike,you're late. Where have you been?
妈妈，我有个新的认识，
Mum. I have been doing some thinking.
女孩子们往往会变得认不出来。
Girls have feelings just like regular people.
Uh hu.
妈妈你知道吗？我今天学到的，
You know mum,I think I have learned more today than
比在学校学那么多年都多。
I have in my entire educational career.
真是好极了。Mike。遇上好老师了。
Well that's great Mike. So do you have good teachers?
也许学校还没有这么好的老师。
Ah,maybe. I'll find out tomorrow when I go to class.
Jason!
JASON。
Mike，已经九点了，你可以了吗？
Mike. Seven o'clock comes early. Let's go pal.
可以了。
Alright.
Carol，明天还要上课呢。
Carol honey. School in the morning.
对。
Alright!
BEN，你得准备睡觉，马上就要关灯了。
Ben. Your long over due lights out now!
别关灯，我怕黑。
No way! I'm afraid of the dark.
你知道，说起来真好笑，我在你这么大的时候，也怕黑暗。……BEN？
You know Ben. This is interesting. When I was your age,I too was...Ben.
别说了爸爸，我爱黑暗！
Forget it dad. I love the dark.